Jehovah Yii Zui Hon (Hovah Yii)

Full Stack Engineer



PHONE +601110501375 EMAIL

LINKS Portfolio, LinkedIn, Github

Profile

Experienced and self-motivated Full-Stack Web and Mobile Application developer with two years of industry experience creating web application and mobile application that emphasizes good UI/UX design. Bringing forth a proven track record of working collaboratively with other developers and designers to achieve goals, increase traffic and visit, and advance the sales cycle of the company. A creative web developer with the ability to understand the needs of his clients and develop personal and unique web pages for his customers.

hovahyii@gmail.com

Employment History

Jun 2017 — Aug 2017

MIRI

Full Stack Web Developer

Mr. Odell Wong

I was introduced to my client, Mr. Odell Wong to develop a full-stack web application for his auto part selling business. I worked with one of his employed designer to come out with the website. Website URL: https://juneautopartmiri.com/

Jan 2020 - Jan 2020

Internships

Jun 2017 - Aug 2017

KUCHING

Robotics Engineer Intern

Then Joon Hiong

I worked as a Robotics Engineer at Standard Modulation Sdn Bhd, a company that makes weather forecast panel. During my intern, I learned to read the schematic drawing of the circuit and electrical components.

Aug 2018 - Sep 2018

KUCHING

Intern at iLead Solution

Careen Chua

Interning at iLead Solution allows me to learn good UI/UX web design. I also learn how to increase web traffic and ranking, especially Google SEO.

Jul 2019 - Aug 2019

BINTULU

Robotics Engineer Intern

Mr. Wil Allen

During my intern at Press Metal, I developed a mobile application to solve the tedious recording process. Mr. Wil who in charge of the production line usually uses paper to record the anode-cathode condition. He is looking for alternatives in order to ease the recording process for himself and his crew and save paper. Then, I proposed to make a mobile application that can help him with the recording process.

Education

Mar 2016 - Jun 2019

KUCHING

Swinburne University of Technology Sarawak Campus

Bachelor of Engineering (Robotics and Mechatronics) (Honours)/Bachelor of Computer Science

I got my Foundation at Swinburne Sarawak and further my degree studies there. Unfortunately, I failed my engineering subjects and also because of financial tension. I was forced to drop out.

Jan 2020 — Jun 2022

MANTIN, NEGERI SEMBILAN

Linton University College

BSc (Hons) in Electronic and Electrical Engineering

I felt lucky as I was offered scholarship studies at this university with my SPM result and portfolio. I think this university is the turning point of my life when I just dropped out of Swinburne and nowhere to go. Given a second chance, I will not waste it and will live my university life to its fullness this time.

Extra-curricular activities

Mar 2019 - Jun 2019

KUCHING

IET Faraday Challenge Sarawak Zone 2019

Swinburne Sarawak Institution of Engineering and Technology (SSIET)

I was one of the pioneer and organizer of the first IET Faraday Challange Sarawak Zone 2019. I planned out the schedule, found my committees and sponsors, invited schools to join the challenge. I worked with Dr Chua Hong Siang and IET Malaysia to organise this event.

Jun 2019 - Nov 2020

KUCHING

Representative for the East Region of Malaysia (2019-2020 Session)

IET Malaysia

I am honored to be accepted as Representative for East Region of Malaysia. I was tasked to coordinate the events and activities for all IET clubs in East Malaysia.

Mar 2019 - May 2019

KUCHING

Young Innovator Challenge (YIC) Mentor

Chumbaka

I joined YIC as mentor. My task is to teach the assigned secondary school students about arduino and programming so that they are prepared for the competition by coming out with their project.

KUCHING

Club Founder & Web Creator

Swinburne Sarawak Computer Science Club

I am the founder of Swinburne Sarawak Computer Science Club and also its website creator.

Visit: scscsarawak.ml

Skills

Bootstrap 4 Microsoft Office HTML & CSS

C Programming
JavaScript

Adobe Photoshop

Adobe Illustrator

Android Development

Java

C#

Editing Video

Flutter

Angular 6



Languages

Chinese English



Malay



References

Careen Chua

iLead Solutions

ask@webdesignkuching.com +60168079658

Wil Allen Anak Bihum

Press Metal Bintulu Sdn Bhd

wilallen@pmbintulu.com +60194743625

Anson

Standard Modulation Sdn Bhd

+60168707008

Hobbies

Reading, programming, jogging